Jude Lim

MS in Computer Science and Applications

Email: Phone:

lkyoong428@gmail.com +1703-679-0990

Location: LinkedIn:

Falls Church, VA, USA https://www.linkedin.com/in/jude-lim-9a2612101/

Github: Website:

https://github.com/KenLim4337/ https://kenlim4337.github.io/

Summary

Master's graduate in Computer Science and Applications at Virginia Tech with a focus on Human Computer Interaction, Data Analytics, and Machine Learning. 5 years of professional experience building web applications with a variety of technologies such as HTML, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), JavaScript, and Python in both front-end and full-stack development.

Skills

Hard Skills

Full Stack Web Development, Data Analytics, Human Computer Interaction (HCI), Machine Learning/AI, User Experience, Conversion Rate Optimization (CRO), Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Soft Skills

Teamwork, Problem Solving, Attention to Detail, Critical Thinking, Verbal Communication, Written Communication, Adaptability

Languages

English (*Native*), Mandarin (*Intermediate*), Cantonese (*Intermediate*), Bahasa Melayu (*Intermediate*)

Education

Virginia Tech 2021 - 2023

Master of Science in Computer Science (GPA: 3.91) Graduate Certificate in Data Analytics

University of Queensland

2014 - 2017

Bachelor of Information Technology (Honors)

Publications

Co-author

Human-in-the-loop for computer vision assurance: A survey

Engineering Applications of Artificial Intelligence, Volume 123, Part B, 2023

Professional Experience

Research Assistant

August 2021 - Present

Crowd Intelligence Lab at Virginia Tech (Arlington, VA, USA)

Designed and developed two Django web development projects.

- Designed and developed Backdrop Explorer, a web-based platform that allows users to search and subsequently sort Civil War portraits based on their background content using a novel Al pipeline (https://vtechworks.lib.vt.edu/handle/10919/115427).
- Redesigned the homepage of Civil War Photo Sleuth, a free, web-based platform and an online community to help identify unknown portraits of soldiers from the American Civil War era (https://doi.org/10.1016/j.engappai.2023.106376).
- Assisted with the writing, editing, and submission of several paper submissions.

Frontend Developer (Conversion Rate Optimization)

February 2018 - July 2021

Conversion Kings (Australia)

Increased conversion rates and revenue for over 40 national and international brands through the development, maintenance and analysis of over 250 A/B tests and web-pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

- Developed pixel-perfect, responsive, cross-browser A/B tests and web-pages based on prototypes provided by designers.
- Reduced project turnaround time and missed bugs by 30% by implementing a standardized user acceptance testing process and managing the testing team...
- Contributed to several large-scale Wordpress web development projects.

Frontend Developer

March 2017 - November 2017

Gliding Queensland (Australia)

Fixed issues with existing Joomla website and constructed a framework for redesigning a Joomla website by providing feedback based on design and development best practices.

Intern

December 2015 - February 2016

KPerak Implementation and Coordination Corporation (Malaysia)

Delivered a full-stack PHP project in the form of an internal employee assessment web application. The project was completed 2 weeks ahead of schedule and subsequently deployed with minimal rework.

Other Experience

Hacker & Crew

July 2017

GovHack 2017 (Australia)

Received honorable mention for the "Going places" national award category by developing a mobile PHP web application that guides users through Brisbane art installations using public bike racks.

Other Certifications

Google Analytics Academy

2019 - 2020

Advanced Google Analytics Google Tag Manager Fundamentals Google Analytics for Beginners

MiTx on edX 2019

15.071x The Analytics Edge

Hobbies and Interests

Cooking, Coffee Roasting, Embroidery